It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a winter fire.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going.
I'll not stay.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean, baby!
No one can make it my dream come true?
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
Well, don't just stand there.
Stop me already.
Is all that fluttering wearing you down?
If you can't take it, why don't
you try groveling, toy soldier?
I thought so.
That confirms it.
All those years ago, that toy soldier
crying like a baby in the rain.
That was the mighty Kiros.
Scarlet!
You're Scarlet's husband.
And Rebecca's father.
It's all connected.
Perfect!
Why, I imagine you've got quite a lot of
bad blood to settle with me, don't you?
That's correct!
Why do you think I came here?
Whoa, not bad!
It seems you found your footing.
But my cape's made of steel. Watch out!
Vyparaglase!
Mother!
Let me fight.
I won't get in your way.
Good call.
Wouldn't want to miss your own funeral.
Right, Rebecca?
I had such a lovely
time killing your wife.
I have to kill your daughter, too.
I'll fight alone.
I want to protect you.
This is my atonement.
For your mother.
And for forcing you to
fight alone all those years.
I'm so ashamed for
putting you through that.
For failing to protect you.
Now that my human form has returned,
I want my daughter to live in peace.
and never swing a sword again.
Uh-oh.
This is not good.
Lao-G is up for the count!
That's some real power.
I think I've heard of these guys before.
The Hapa Sui army from Kano.
I'll be careful.
Anyone can become an enemy at any time.
Hey, Gramps!
Come on, wake up!
Don't die! Not now!
I'll reserve two event venues
for us real soon, okay, sweetie?
Venues? For what?
One for our wedding, of course!
And then the funeral.
He's not dead!
Stand up, Gladius!
You don't want to die crawling on
the ground like a beast, do you?
Now fight!
Don't make me wait!
This should shut you up.
Gladius!
Wait, you can't!
He's turned the whole area into a bomb.
You know what happens next.
You've been plotting this
for ages now, haven't you?
Hey, Bartolomeo!
Everything in the area is about to blow.
Let me inside your barrier, quick.
Not a chance. Why not?
If I open it, that'll put
me and Miss Robin in danger.
Also, enemies might sneak in.
But I'm your ally.
You can't just leave
me to die, gladius sir.
You're gonna blow us up too.
You'll be fine.
You're professionals after all.
Let me in.
Pop rock fest.
Farewell, Cavendish.
If you'd been stuck out there, that
would've wiped you out for sure.
Exactly!
So why'd you wait until the last second?
I could've died!
How about a thank you?
Is that any way to act towards
someone who just saved your life?
I've been out there
fighting all on my own.
Where's my thank you? Bite me!
That's enough.
Let me out of here.
We need to win! Really?
You scream at me and beg to come
in and now you want out again?
Can't stick around for five
minutes just to be polite?
Show some manners!
It's not your house!
We're fighting a battle, okay?
Time for offense!
I'm not letting you in next time!
If I'm about to die, you'd better!
Do you want to win this fight or not?
Ugh!
We'll settle this later!
Crap, Miss Robin!
Okay, she's doing fine.
That's all that matters.
I'll be there soon, Rebecca. Stay safe.
You cunning little tramp.
How dare you?
You've caused the
executives enough trouble.
This ends now.
Catapult Pop!
Variability!
Back it!
Damn it!
I thought I'd blown him up!
Take it to the bank, Miss Robin!
I got you back!
Oh, Rooster, thank you!
I can't believe it.
She just winked at me.
Oh, yeah, that's the stuff.
She was totally like,
thanks, little rooster.
You can be my slave.
I'll even step on you
if you behave, right?
Okay, okay, sorry.
Gotta check yourself, Bato.
Keep that one in the realm of fantasy.
Anyway, dude, this is good stuff.
I'm hyped.
Huh? Cavendish?
You're behind the barrier, too?
Unfortunately for you, Gladius.
Blade of Beauty! Brachio!
Gladius, help!
Bottle of mayo?
Barrier balls!
It protects him when
it's crushing all of us!
Thanks, Miss Robin.
All it takes is one little wink, and
my heart lights up like an inferno!
Okay, Bartolomeo, that's enough!
You're gonna crush your ally!
Sorry, Cabbage, but there's a
good reason why I can't stop!
What might that be?
Cause I'm feeling super jazzed, baby!
Oh, that's lovely!
I'm high as a kite!
Can't stop this train!
WE 'LL HIT THE EMERGENCY BREAK, MORON!
NO CAN DO!
Dellinger! Hm?
Uh...
Haven't you cleaned up
the second level yet?
Hey, Gladius!
Going for a jog?
I'll join you in a sec, okay?
Alright, but make it quick!
Nico Robin is climbing to the top,
and I can't stop her because my
hands are full with these two idiots!
Ah-ha! That's funny!
I can't wait to join the party!
I said ignore me at your own peril.
We're not finished yet.
You don't know how to
take a hint, do you, Mr.
Longarm?
So you've been hiding your extra joints
in those weird shoulder thingies.
That's kind of creepy, really.
I know you're a champion fighter, but
you've got a hole in your stomach.
Just drop dead already.
This is a man's world, and that
means I'm bound by a sense of duty.
To all those brave fighters
who fell before me.
How noble of you.
If you'd played dead, I
might have spared your life.
What is the point of standing up now, huh?
I can still buy time at least.
I hope that's enough.
All we have to do is keep
you busy until Straw Hat.
Bounce the tar out of Doflamingo.
So beat me if you like.
But the only victory that matters,
I'll win with my allies as a team.
So instead of calling it defeat,
you call it a noble sacrifice?
Spoken like a true loser, sense
of duty is a shackle for the weak.
Oh,
my God.
I'm no ordinary human, either.
The strength of a fighting fish
courses through every muscle.
I'm here, Gladius!
You still need my help?
Where'd you go?
Gladius, hello?
Dellinger, go back down.
It's too dangerous here.
There's a deadly enemy!
That doesn't sound like you.
Come on, I've seen the competition,
and if we team up, there's
nobody that can beat us.
Dillinger!
Damn it.
He's finished.
Whoa, jeez.
What is going on out there?
That little creep with the horns.
And all the soldiers totally ate it.
One dude did all of that.
Oh, man.
That guy's freaky as hell.
What is up with that face?
Wait.
Who is that?
He's dressed like cabbage,
but that can't be him.
I mean, can it?
Wait a sec.
Something just like this happened back
at the Coliseum during the D-Block fight.
I'm speechless, folks.
Just like that, the
whole ring is out cold.
He cleared out those gladiators
in the blink of an eye.
The clothes, the hair,
the sword, all Cavendish.
But that face is somebody else's dish.
So what kind of dish are
we dealing with here?
Huh?
That was too fast to even see.
Holy crap, this guy's scary.
Hey, creepy face, who are you?
You can zip around as fast as you
like, but you're not getting in,
even if you ask nicely.
What do you want to kill me for anyway?
If you're mad about me kicking
you out earlier, get over it.
What were you looking at
up there, you big weirdo?
Don't get any funny ideas, okay?
Hey, are you listening to me?
Oh, no!
You come back here and fight me! Leave Ms.
Rocket alone!
Why don't you calm down?
You're not going anywhere on my watch.
That's quite a wicked look on your face?
Poor cabbage.
Do you need something?
I'm sorry, but I don't have time to play.
Rebecca needs me
Whoa, she stopped him! What a move!
This Robin is so cool!
What was I thinkin',
sayin' I would protect you when I so
clearly pale before your brilliance?
Dammit! Akubar!
I didn't give you permission to do this!
You cannot come out right now!
I didn't mean to do that.
Forgive me for attacking you.
I've heard word of your deadly alter ego.
Hakuba, right?
That was him.
He's quite the monster.
He goes after anyone he sees.
first i'll take your arms and
legs then i'll chop your whole
body into tiny pieces niko
robin no one can escape my blade
would you go away now is not the time
shut up why don't you go back to sleep you
don't understand the
importance of this fight
i have a personal debt
to repay i'll turn this
place into a sea of
blood this battle is my
responsibility i don't
care i'll rip this woman
to shreds he must have a
split personality unless
this is just how he makes
decisions my body my
Kuba, this fight is mine!
Now he's half cabbage and half psycho!
I have had enough!
This body belongs to me!
You was half and half just a second ago!
Alright, I think he's
gone now. Please, Robin.
Could you release me from your grip?
Let you go?
After what I just saw?
You're fine right where you are.
I'll take my revenge
on both of you at once.
Even if you try to fly away, you can't
escape the blast radius of the entire wall
Cut that out!
There's no way we'll survive up here.
You need to abandon the plan
for now, let's get down.
I can't, and the time that takes,
Rebecca could be badly hurt?
Don't worry, I got this!
You keep your damn explosions
away from Miss Robin!
That's a surprisingly sound judgment
If you defeat me, it will
indeed cancel the rupture.
Pop hair!
I'm all numb. What'd you do?
Those hairs are poison needles. What?
Are you all right?
This is the power of the pop-pop fruit.
From head to toe, I am a rupture man!
If you do harm to me, my
whole body will burst,
and thousands of those poison
needles that handily thwarted you?
will pierce your two friends up above.
Of course, if you don't harm
me, the wall will explode.
So, which shall it be?
keep in mind that the explosion of
my body will kill you as well I'm
not worried about me getting wrecked
but it seems like miss Robin gets
hurt either way well look at you
such a fast learner come on don't let
him get under your skin keep your
eyes on the prize Bato what's your
priority right now that's obvious
I gotta protect miss Robert if I
want to stop the explosion I gotta
bust stop this fat-ass hedgehog dude
but then there's the poison needle
thing which will hurt robin as well
i gotta think outside the box here
come on brain think no think harder
wait a sec what if there's some way i
could sacrifice cabbage to save miss robin
i got an idea cabbage i'm gonna beat up
the hedgehog guy to stop the explosion
Then when the poison things shoot out,
you act as a human shield and make
sure none of them hit Miss Robin.
Idiot. Did you hear me?
Shut up, Roaster.
Cabbage got all evil again.
We got an emergency here and he
can't keep his head on straight.
Miss Robin's in danger
from Bad Cabbage, too.
I need a plan right now.
That's it.
You decided to attack me.
I can only put up one barrier
at a time, but that's okay.
That's all I need to pull this off,
as long as I can save Miss Robin,
I won't think twice.
I got. No regrets!
Perrier ball!
You can blow a ball you like, fatso!
Nothing's getting past that barrier!
It's just you and me!
Krister, stop!
What are you?
Going to sacrifice yourself,
are you? Fine then!
Fashion Pup!
Booster, no!
Suck on that, you stupid hedgehog.
I shut you down and I
shut down your wall bomb.
I saved Miss Robin.
What more could I ever ask for?
Nice try, but your aim needs work.
You missed by just a few centimeters.
In other words, it was my shoulder
you stabbed, not my throat.
No!
I was so close!
Since he was so big and round,
I couldn't tell what was what!
Damn it!
You're a power holder as well.
So you know how this works.
As long as I'm conscious,
the effects of my ability persist.
Now since you can't move, you can sit
there and watch your friends explode.
How did I screw this up so bad? Damn it!
I'm so stupid!
Forgive me for that lapse just now.
This is Cavendish.
I've brought Hakuba under control again,
but I have allowed him to
borrow half of my body.
Now let go of me, so that I can kill you!
I'll use Hakuba's speed to help
you escape to the Sunflower Field.
Otherwise, we'll all explode
when the bomb goes off!
There's no other option left.
Please, let go!
You have to trust me!
Which one?
There's no time to think!
Hurry!
No!
You bested!
Pop Rock!
Super Arena!
Miss Robbie!
Your barrier was useful after all.
Look, both of them gone without a trace.
Why'd you stop me?
You're hurting your own body!
If I'm willing to take things this far,
maybe you should listen to me.
Sien Fleur!
Spider-Man, hurry!
You protected me.
Your hand stopped Hakuba's sword.
What a complicated man.
Absurd.
How could they escape
from a rupture that size?
I should be ashamed of myself,
thinking that I was good enough
to stand beside his loofiness.
Homage, holy fest!
Mr. Luffy,
I know I've still got a long way to go,
but I swear I'll get stronger and stronger.
Barrier, barrier!
Then, when I'm strong enough,
maybe someday I'll be a man
who's worthy of helping you!
PISTOL!
Had to borrow a little of
your strength there, Mr.
Luffy. Thanks.
Man, what a pain.
I'm never teaming up with cabbage
again, that dude's annoying as hell.
Sounds like they're having
a real party down there.
Speaking of parties.
It seems like all this rocking and rolling
is too much even for seasoned gladiators.
Right Rebecca.
Rebecca, you can't block that!
Swift pedals to sway his blade.
Mille Fleur, now!
Butterfly! Mark it!
Just in time.
You saved me!
Son of a...
Robiland!
You finished your mission, Rebecca.
I'm grateful.
Now it's my turn to lend you a hand.
Stand back.
Let me take care of them.
Thank you.